Finding Aid for Library Planning Committee (University of Michigan) records, 1970-1976
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Library Planning Committee (University of Michigan) records 1970-1976
University of Michigan. Library Planning Committee.
0.6 linear feet
87189 Bimu C410 2
Records, 1970-1976, of a University of Michigan library committee concerned with coordinating and proposing library planning activities. Includes summary minutes, reports, survey materials, and task force records.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were donated by Peggy Ann Kusnerz (donor no. 5158 ) in March 1986.
The record group is open without restriction.
Frederick H. Wagman, Director of the University Library, established the University Library Planning Committee on September 1, 1973. The committee's charge included responsibility for identifying planning activities throughout the library, specifying areas where additional planning was required, recommending priorities among several planning activities, and proposing organizational patterns for future planning activity. The committee's work was concluded in 1974 when it presented its report to Director Wagman.
The Library Planning Committee records date from 1970 to 1976 and measure less than one linear foot. They include minutes, reports, survey materials and detailed records from two of the many task forces, which explored specific areas of concern.
Subjects:
Libraries--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; University of Michigan. Library.
- Records
  - General, 1970-1973 and 1976 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Draft and Final Reports, 1974, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Survey, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Task Forces
    - General (Box 1)
    - Reports, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Task Force 11: Non-Print Media (Box 1)
    - Task Force 21: Working Conditions (Box 1)